<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ResearchProjectDefs>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchTargetingModule</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: targeting module</label>
    <description>   Mining &amp; Co. used to provide its clients some security assets to protect their mining operations.
Your researchers want to reverse engineer some targeting module that felt from the crashed ship with your drop-pods.

- Reverse engineer targeting modules.
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   Your scientists have sucessfully reverse engineered the targeting module.
You will soon be able to make your own advanced weapons.
    
- You can now build the security workbench.
- You can now make targeting modules.
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>1000</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchIntegratedCircuits</li>
    </prerequisites>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchLaserRifle</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: laser rifle</label>
    <description>   Use the new targeting module to develop a standard laser weapon.
 
- Develop a new kind of energy weapon: the laser rifle.
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   You have developped a new weapon type: the laser rifle.
This is an all-rounded gun. Its lack of punch is compensated by its high range and precision.

- You can now make weapons parts at the security workbench. Those parts are used during weapon crafting.
- You can now make laser rifles at the security workbench.
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>800</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchTargetingModule</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchMods>
      <li>
        <specialAction>Weapons.Building_SecurityWorkbench.TryAddRecipesMakeWeaponPartsAndMakeLaserRifle</specialAction>
      </li>
    </researchMods>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchPrismRifle</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: prism rifle</label>
    <description>   Sometimes, accuracy and long range is just not enough, especially when pirates are dropping right on your heads!

- Adapt the standard laser rifle to trade accuracy and range for pure power at close range.
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   Your scientists have replaced the standard laser rifle targeting module by an additional energy pack.
They have also attached a flawless crysteel at the cannon mouth to maximize the impacted area.
The result is a powerful shock rifle at close range.

- You can now refit standard laser rifles into prism rifles at the security workbench.
- Given their extreme rarity, buying crysteel from traders is the most reliable way.
- However, you can still try to extract crysteel from plasteel yourself... if you can afford it!
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>800</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchLaserRifle</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchMods>
      <li>
        <specialAction>Weapons.Building_SecurityWorkbench.TryAddRecipesExtractCrysteelAndMakePrismRifle</specialAction>
      </li>
    </researchMods>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchLaserGatling</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: laser gatling</label>
    <description>   Dealing with crowd is not an easy task with a single laser beam. But what about a volley of small yet effective ones?

- Adapt the standard laser rifle into a rapid-firing laser gatling.
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   You have developped a new weapon type: the laser gatling.
Each shot is weak but still efficient at burning one's retina. How do you think all those pirates earned their eye-patch?
The range and relative precision of this gun is balanced by its weight (but who cares in a power armor?).

- You can now make laser gatlings at the security workbench.
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>1000</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchLaserRifle</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchMods>
      <li>
        <specialAction>Weapons.Building_SecurityWorkbench.TryAddRecipeMakeLaserGatling</specialAction>
      </li>
    </researchMods>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <!--<ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchHeavyLasgun</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: heavy lasgun</label>
    <description>   Those pesky power-armors are well reinforced againt standard bullets. But how will they deal with a massive energy beam?

- Adapt the standard laser rifle into a powerfull heavy lasgun.
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   You have developped a new weapon type: the heavy lasgun.
This is a powerfull gun against heavy-armored target. Its strength comes at the cost of a low firing rate and range.

- You can now make heavy lasguns at the security workbench.
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>300</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchLaserRifle</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchMods>
      <li>
        <specialAction>Weapons.Building_SecurityWorkbench.TryAddRecipeMakeHeavyLasgun</specialAction>
      </li>
    </researchMods>
  </ResearchProjectDef>-->

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchHighPrecisionLasgun</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: high precision lasgun</label>
    <description>   Your researchers can improve the targeting capabilities of a weapon by interfacing several targeting modules.

- Adapt the standard laser rifle into a high precision lasgun.
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   You have developped a new weapon type: the high precision lasgun.
Make each shot count with this sharp-shooter weapon. While its damage is not so high, its relatively high firing rate is remarkable for such long-range gun.

- You can now make high precision lasguns at the security workbench.
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>1200</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchLaserRifle</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchMods>
      <li>
        <specialAction>Weapons.Building_SecurityWorkbench.TryAddRecipeMakeHighPrecisionLasgun</specialAction>
      </li>
    </researchMods>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

</ResearchProjectDefs>